{
    "subject": "resource/Roddy_Bottum",
    "predicate": "property/occupation",
    "object": "resource/Keyboardist",
    "human_readable": "Roddy Bottum's occupation is Keyboardist.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8632888793945312,
            "question": "What is Roddy Bottum's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.540816068649292,
            "question": "Are there any other musical skills besides playing keyboard that Roddy Bottum might possess?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5291393399238586,
            "question": "What kind of music is often associated with keyboardist roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44756972789764404,
            "question": "What instrument does Roddy Bottum play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4205871820449829,
            "question": "Can you name a famous musician who plays the same instrument as Roddy Bottum?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41786107420921326,
            "question": "What are some famous bands or artists that feature a prominent keyboardist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3758031725883484,
            "question": "What role does Roddy Bottum typically fulfill in a band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36161327362060547,
            "question": "How does the role of a keyboardist contribute to a musical performance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2824944257736206,
            "question": "In what musical context does Roddy Bottum work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14544978737831116,
            "question": "Can you think of any historical periods where keyboard instruments were particularly popular?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Roddy Bottum's occupation is Keyboardist.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7767_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what musical context does Roddy Bottum work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7767_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the role of a keyboardist contribute to a musical performance?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7767_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What role does Roddy Bottum typically fulfill in a band?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7767_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7767_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7767_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7767_147.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7767_173.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7767_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7767_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7767_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7767_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7767_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7767_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain multiple mentions of Roddy Bottum being a keyboardist for Faith No More, and also mention him as such in various contexts. This supports the triple that Roddy Bottum's occupation is Keyboardist."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided consistently refer to Roddy Bottum as a keyboardist, particularly for the band Faith No More. This supports the statement that his occupation is keyboardist."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}